Muhammad Waleed Bin Tariq

Pakistan



muh.wbt@gmail.com

+923347111446



https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-waleed-807636217

Summary

I am a Dot Net developer and a React developer. I have experience working as a freelancer in different projects. I develop good quality and responsive web pages. As a developer, I make modular, clean, object-oriented, and well-commented code, always aiming for quality and intelligence in the solutions. My solutions are complete, front-end.

I have experience with:

- √ C-Sharp
- √ Dot Net
- √ React JS
- √ Next JS
- √ Jet Brains IDE
- √ JavaScript | jQuery | React JS
- √ HTML/CSS

Experience

Software Developer

Computer & Networking Services (CNS)

MAR 2023 - Present

In this era of technological advancements, computerized access control and surveillance systems have become one of the most important resources to organizations. An automated system, access control and circulation control of all personnel authorized entry into a restricted/controlled area will provide greater reliability.

React JS Developer (Hybrid)

Data Majority

DEC 2022 - Present

This job role involves front-end development. It is a very great experience working at Data Majority specifically in Lead role of Front-End taking on the challenges based on customer requirements/projects and delivering them on time and with utmost quality.

Font-end Developer

Freelance

JULY 2022 - SEP 2022

This job role involves the front-end development of an ecommerce website. It is a very great experience working at Data Majority specifically in Lead role of Front-End taking on the challenges based on customer requirements/projects and delivering them on time and with utmost quality.

Education



🤛 Comsats University Islamabad

BS(Computer Science)

2018 - 2022

Punjab Group of Colleges Rahim Yar Khan

Intermediate/Matric

2016 - 2018

Skills

• React JS • JavaScript • XML • Web Applications • HTML • Next JS • Angular • Dot Net • C-Sharp